mirrorstack.com 2014-07-01

# MirrorStack - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

1\. Logging IP Addresses

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server does not recognize any information regarding the domain or e-mail address. IP addresses are logged and used by MirroStack for measuring usage.  

2\. Collecting e-mail Addresses 

We automatically collect certain information about your computer when you visit our website, for example, the e-mail addresses of MirroStack Delivery recipients and senders for the purpose of logging and measuring usage. MirroStack does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with nonaffiliated companies.

3\. Certain Exceptional Disclosures 

We may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct or potential threats to the physical safety of any person. Disclosure may be required by law or in connection with any legal process.

4.Which data does Mirrorcreator store about the files I upload?

\- IP address of the computer from which the upload is started  
\- Time of the upload  
\- The e-mail address entered by the uploader

5\. Use of Cookies 

MirroStack uses cookies to store the preferences and tracking trends of users. You can always choose not to receive a cookie file by enabling your web browser to refuse cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie. However, MirroStack doese not use any methods for tracking users (the so-called spy or gif images and so on).

6\. How we protect your information 

We make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. 

We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required.

7\. External Links

If any part of the MirroStack.com website links you to other websites, those websites do not operate under this Privacy Policy. We recommend you examine the privacy statements posted on those other websites to understand their procedures for collecting, using and disclosing personal information.

8\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

By using MirrorStack.com, you consent to the collection and use of these informations by Mirrorcreator. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
